export const users = [
    {
        userName: 'Atreides095',
        password: 'password',
        test: true,
        decks: [
            {
                name: 'japanese colors',
                picture: '',
                tags: ['japanese', 'colors', 'beginner'],
                cards: [
                    {
                        front: '青い',
                        back: 'blue/green',
                    },

                    {
                        front: '赤い',
                        back: 'red',
                    },
                    {
                        front: '黒い',
                        back: 'black',
                    },
                    {
                        front: '白い',
                        back: 'white',
                    },
                ],
            },
            {
                name: 'spanish colors',
                picture: '',
                tags: ['japanese', 'colors', 'beginner'],
                cards: [
                    {
                        front: 'azul',
                        back: 'blue',
                    },

                    {
                        front: 'rojo',
                        back: 'red',
                    },
                    {
                        front: 'negro',
                        back: 'black',
                    },
                    {
                        front: 'blanco',
                        back: 'white',
                    },
                ],
            },
            {
                name: 'spanish days of the week',
                picture: '',
                tags: ['japanese', 'colors', 'beginner'],
                cards: [
                    {
                        front: 'lunes',
                        back: 'monday',
                    },

                    {
                        front: 'martes',
                        back: 'tuesday',
                    },
                    {
                        front: 'miércoles',
                        back: 'wednesday',
                    },
                    {
                        front: 'jueves',
                        back: 'thursday',
                    },
                    {
                        front: 'viernes',
                        back: 'friday',
                    },
                ],
            },
        ],
    },
];
